<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JSblog</title>
    <link>jsevo.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on JSblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;#xA9; 2017 Jonas Schl&amp;uuml;ter. All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="jsevo.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is Jonas?</title>
      <link>jsevo.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jsevo.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Jonas. I&amp;rsquo;m scientist currently living in New York City. I moved here after having started a machine-learning based legal tech business  with three friends in London last year.
In 2014, I finished my PhD in Computational Biology at Oxford University, where I was supervised by Kevin Foster. After that, I moved to Japan on a JSPS fellowship to work with Hisashi Ohstuki on game-theoretical models of evolution. I am now based at Memorial Sloan Kettering where I am working with Joao Xavier on developing new machine learning approaches to analyze microbiota data from cancer patients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Observations on crypto currency markets and South Korean political developments.</title>
      <link>jsevo.github.io/post/cryptocurrency/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jsevo.github.io/post/cryptocurrency/</guid>
      <description>I am here reporting a few observations on recent market movements in the cryptocurrency trade that coincide with highly unusual political events in South Korea. None of what I will write in the following should be understood as a definite explanation of the recent behavior of the cryptocurrency markets. Such an oversimplification would be preposterous. There are many moving parts in this market&amp;mdash;and the development of blockchain technology as a business&amp;mdash;that certainly many of them had stronger roles in the market dynamics than the points presented here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>